Kenneth Shelley

Software Engineer (678) 378-9652

|Github.com/SoftwareKengineer||Linkedin.com/in/SoftwareKengineer||SoftwareKengineer@gmail.com

Creative software engineer with the ability to pick up new languages and technologies as needed. Prior to being a software engineer, I worked in leading roles or independently where I had to rely on self-accountability to ensure success.

Software Development Skills

 Debugging, JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React, Express, Redux, RESTful API, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Bootstrap, Flexbox, AWS, React Native, HTML, CSS, Java

Education

DigitalCrafts | Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development | Atlanta, GA

Nov 2022 - June 2023

 Full-Stack Web Development training program covering full-stack development including, but not limited to JavaScript, Python, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like React/Redux and server-side technologies including Node is, Express, and PostgreSQL.

Software Development Portfolio

Map of Currency | github.com/SoftwareKengineer/MapOfCurrency

Feb 2023

- Led development efforts for a currency exchange webpage using multiple APIs
- User experience allows for the ability to interact with a map that allows users to compare local currencies to a preselected currency for up to date exchange rates.
- Front-end application built with HTML, JavaScript, Bootstrap, APIs

Professional Work Experience

Superior Water Services | Water Treatment Technologist

Feb 2019 – Aug 2022

- Maintain industrial HVAC systems through water treatment and analysist.
- Trained inbound employees on how to gather water samples and input data to effectively mitigate HVAC corrosion, prevent dissolved solids build up and kill microbials in the system.
- Managed warehouse inventory and blended chemical for effective water treatment.

Nutrisystem Inc. | Customer service/ Sales

Jan 2015 – May 2017

- Managed copious amounts of inbound calls and outbound calls in a timely manner
- Built sustainable relationships and engaged customers per metrics
- Achieved and exceeded sales metric while assisting in any customer issues

KPS Real Estate Acquisitions, LLC | Acquisitions Manager

March 2011 - May 2014

- Secured investment capital
- Closed numerous investment properties
- Worked closely with Real estate Investors to help maximize investment returns
- Created an automated system to generate leads from home owners in need of liquidating their property/ properties.